I heard that
سمعت ان
there have been a lot of big events these days.
كان هناك الكثير من الأحداث الكبيرة هذه الأيام.
Yes. First,
نعم.  أولاً،
the late emperor passed away,
توفي الإمبراطور الراحل ،
King Lin'an ascended the throne,
اعتلى الملك لينان العرش ،
the most unexpected thing is,
أكثر شيء غير متوقع هو
The new emperor actually married his father's daughter-in-law,
تزوج الإمبراطور الجديد بالفعل من زوجة ابن والده ،
and the empress is a peerless beauty.
والإمبراطورة ذات جمال منقطع النظير.
He's actually a fat man.
إنه في الواقع رجل سمين.
You should know that as soon as the late emperor ascended the throne,
يجب أن تعلم أنه بمجرد أن تولى الإمبراطور الراحل العرش ،
it was promulgated.
صدر.
A woman's weight is the rule of a lowly family,
وزن المرأة حكم الأسرة المتواضعة ،
except for those powerful families,
باستثناء تلك العائلات القوية ،
It shows how much the late emperor hated fat women.
إنه يوضح مدى كره الإمبراطور الراحل للنساء البدينات.
How could she marry a fat queen?
كيف يمكن أن تتزوج ملكة سمينة؟
Yes,
نعم،
I heard that the character "Queen" is very popular,
سمعت أن شخصية "كوين" تحظى بشعبية كبيرة ،
The phoenix was born,
ولدت طائر الفينيق ،
so the late emperor was seriously ill,
لذلك كان الإمبراطور الراحل مريضًا بشكل خطير ،
I had no choice but to let her enter the palace
لم يكن لدي خيار سوى السماح لها بالدخول إلى القصر
and put someone beside Su You'an in joy.
وأفرح شخصًا بجانب سو يوآن.
Have you got any news?
هل حصلت على أي أخبار؟
Master,
يتقن،
There's no news yet.
ليس هناك أخبار حتى الآن.
Su Jinxia is the apple of Su You'an's eye.
Su Jinxia هي تفاحة عين Su You'an.
The war between us and the Eastern Jue Dynasty,
الحرب بيننا وبين أسرة جويه الشرقية ،
is very anxious,
قلق جدا ،
If something happens to his daughter,
إذا حدث شيء لابنته ،
I'm afraid General Su will have a reaction.
أخشى أن الجنرال سو سيكون لديه رد فعل.
Keep an eye on the empress,
راقب الإمبراطورة ،
and protect her safety.
وحماية سلامتها.
Report to me at any time.
أبلغني في أي وقت.
Yes, Your Highness.
نعم سموكم.
Forget about the late emperor,
انسى الامبراطور الراحل ،
but the new emperor is still young,
لكن الإمبراطور الجديد لا يزال شابًا ،
Why did you marry a fat queen like her?
لماذا تزوجت من ملكة سمينة مثلها؟
You're not going to be happy, are you?
لن تكون سعيدا ، أليس كذلك؟
You don't know that.
أنت لا تعرف ذلك.
The new emperor doesn't care if the empress is fat or thin?
الإمبراطور الجديد لا يهتم إذا كانت الإمبراطورة سمينة أم نحيفة؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I heard that the new emperor has passed the year of weak crown,
سمعت أن الإمبراطور الجديد قد تجاوز عام التاج الضعيف ،
but he is not close to women.
لكنه ليس قريبًا من النساء.
He doesn't have any concubines,
ليس لديه محظيات ،
because he's addicted
لأنه مدمن
to Dragon Yang,
إلى Dragon Yang ،
Dragon Yang Freak,
التنين الغريب
Your Highness, keep your voice down.
صاحب السمو ، أخفض صوتك.
If anyone hears this,
إذا سمع أحد هذا ،
they'll kill you.
سيقتلونك.
I'm telling you.
أنا أخبرك.
There are no concubines in the harem,
لا توجد محظيات في الحريم ،
only me.
انا فقط.
So it's because of this.
لذلك هذا بسبب هذا.
But it's just a rumor.
لكنها مجرد شائعة.
It can't be true.
لا يمكن أن يكون ذلك صحيحًا.
Yes.
نعم.
Got it.
فهمتك.
You too.
أنت أيضاً.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
you ate all eight drumsticks.
أكلت كل أفخاذ الطبل الثمانية.
you are now the empress,
أنت الآن الإمبراطورة ،
Pay attention to your manners.
انتبه إلى آدابك.
It's so boring to be the empress.
إنه أمر ممل للغاية أن تكون الإمبراطورة.
You can't do this.
لا يمكنك فعل هذا.
You can't do that.
لا يمكنك فعل ذلك.
What's the difference between him and a prisoner?
ما الفرق بينه وبين السجين؟
Also,
أيضًا،
don't you think Qin Molin is strange?
ألا تعتقد أن تشين مولين غريب؟
Overnight,
بين عشية وضحاها،
I changed from the Empress Dowager to the Empress.
لقد تغيرت من الإمبراطورة الأرملة إلى الإمبراطورة.
She changed from a stepmother to a wife.
لقد تغيرت من زوجة أبي إلى زوجة.
Do you all play like this?
هل تلعبون كلكم هكذا؟
It's so exciting.
إنه مثير للغاية.
Your Highness
صاحب السمو
It's disrespectful to call His Majesty by his first name,
من غير المحترم أن ننادي جلالة الملك باسمه الأول ،
but fortunately no one heard it.
لكن لحسن الحظ لم يسمعها أحد.
However,
لكن،
His Majesty made Her Highness the empress,
جلالة الملك جعل صاحبة السمو الإمبراطورة ،
Of course it's because Her Highness is the best.
بالطبع لأن صاحبة السمو هي الأفضل.
Silly girl,
فتاة سخيفة،
there must be a conspiracy.
يجب أن تكون هناك مؤامرة.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
what kind of person
أي نوع من الأشخاص
is Qin Molin?
هو تشين مولين؟
Well,
نحن سوف،
I'm not sure about that either,
لست متأكدًا من ذلك أيضًا ،
His Majesty is ranked 13th,
جلالة الملك في المرتبة 13 ،
I heard that his birth mother is a maid,
سمعت أن والدته هي خادمة ،
He passed away when he was very young.
توفي عندما كان صغيرا جدا.
His Majesty has always been unfavored,
لطالما كان جلالة الملك غير مرغوب فيه ،
and other princes often bully His Majesty,
وغالبًا ما يتنمر الأمراء الآخرون على جلالة الملك ،
But
لكن
three years ago,
منذ ثلاثة أعوام،
His Majesty suddenly stands out
جلالة الملك يبرز فجأة
from many princes.
من العديد من الأمراء.
Show your amazing talent.
أظهر موهبتك الرائعة.
The late emperor was so delighted
كان الإمبراطور الراحل سعيدًا جدًا
that he was appointed as the King of Lin'an.
أنه تم تعيينه ملكًا على لينان.
And then he inherited the throne,
ثم ورث العرش ،
I'm afraid it wasn't all of a sudden.
أخشى أن الأمر لم يكن مفاجئًا.
It was premeditated.
كان مع سبق الإصرار.
Keeping a low profile
الحفاظ على الانظار
and accumulating wealth.
ومراكمة الثروة.
In this palace,
في هذا القصر
it's a trick.
هذه خدعة.
There are many rules.
هناك العديد من القواعد.
Where is Qin Molin?
أين تشين مولين؟
He's scheming and hard
إنه مكيد وصعب
to figure out.
لمعرفة ذلك.
It seems that I'd better
يبدو أنني أفضل
leave the palace early.
مغادرة القصر مبكرا.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
you're not trying to
أنت لا تحاول
escape from the palace.
الهروب من القصر.
No, no, no.
لا لا لا.
Absolutely not.
بالطبع لا.
Your Highness, you are a daughter of a noble family,
سموك أنت بنت عائلة نبيلة
and you have been pampered since childhood.
وقد تم تدليلكم منذ الصغر.
If you leave the palace,
إذا غادرت القصر ،
how can you survive?
كيف تستطيع النجاة
How to survive?
كيف تنجو؟
I can go back to my old job.
يمكنني العودة إلى وظيفتي القديمة.
To open a women's clothing store in ancient times,
لفتح متجر لبيع الملابس النسائية في العصور القديمة ،
to introduce modern clothing,
لإدخال الملابس الحديثة ،
Business must be good.
يجب أن يكون العمل جيدًا.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Who attacked me with drumsticks?
من هاجمني بأعواد الطبل؟
Oh,
أوه،
Isn't this Her Highness?
أليست هذه صاحبة السمو؟
Watch
راقب
It's much rounder than on the day of the empress
إنها أكثر استدارة مما كانت عليه في يوم الإمبراطورة
dowager ceremony.
حفل الأرملة.
She's His Majesty's foster sister.
إنها أخت صاحب الجلالة الحاضنة.
Lin Rouyi.
لين روي.
It looks
يبدو
familiar.
معروف.
Why are you looking at me like that?
لماذا تنظر الي هكذا؟
It scares Rouyi so much.
إنه يخيف روي كثيراً.
It turns out that since ancient times,
اتضح أنه منذ العصور القديمة ،
witches have always looked the same.
لقد بدت الساحرات دائمًا متشابهات.
What are you doing, Your Highness?
ماذا تفعل يا صاحب السمو؟
original
أصلي
You also know that I'm the empress.
أنت تعرف أيضًا أنني الإمبراطورة.
You are not allowed to speak without permission.
لا يسمح لك بالتحدث بدون إذن.
I'll do it in front of me.
سأفعل ذلك أمامي.
Have you learned
هل تعلمت
all your rules?
كل القواعد الخاصة بك؟
Do you know what kind of crime
هل تعرف أي نوع من الجريمة
it is to do this?
هو أن تفعل هذا؟
You haven't watched the palace drama in vain for so many years,
لم تشاهد دراما القصر عبثا لسنوات عديدة ،
but you've come in handy.
لكنك أصبحت في متناول يدي.
His Majesty is here.
جلالة الملك هنا.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالة الملك.
Brother,
أخ،
my head is so dizzy.
رأسي بالدوار جدا.
I know how to pretend to be dizzy.
أعرف كيف أتظاهر بالدوار.
Oh,
أوه،
Brother Emperor, I'm so dizzy too.
الأخ الإمبراطور ، أنا مصاب بدوار شديد أيضًا.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
I hurt the dragon's body.
لقد آذيت جسد التنين.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
it's all me.
كل شيء عني.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
I hurt His Majesty.
لقد جرحت جلالته.
I feel guilty in my heart,
أشعر بالذنب في قلبي ،
which is hard to describe.
وهو ما يصعب وصفه.
I wish
أتمنى
the one who got hurt was me,
أنا من تأذى ،
Your Majesty, punish me.
جلالة الملك ، عاقبني.
I'm willing to take it no matter what?
أنا على استعداد لأخذها مهما كان الأمر؟
How?
كيف؟
No complaints,
لا يوجد شكاوى،
right?
الصحيح؟
I told you it's so touching,
أخبرتك أنه مؤثر جدًا ،
but you still have the nerve to punish me?
ولكن لا يزال لديك الجرأة لمعاقبتي؟
Originally,
في الأصل،
I wanted to ask the empress,
أردت أن أسأل الإمبراطورة ،
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
But I didn't expect that
لكنني لم أتوقع ذلك
I'm so important to Her Highness.
أنا مهم جدا لسمو السمو.
My injury has made Her Highness feel so guilty.
جعلت إصابتي صاحبة السمو تشعر بالذنب الشديد.
Since the empress has proposed punishment,
منذ أن اقترحت الإمبراطورة العقوبة ،
if I don't follow the empress's wishes,
إذا لم أتبع رغبات الإمبراطورة ،
I'm afraid the empress will have trouble sleeping and eating.
أخشى أن تواجه الإمبراطورة مشكلة في النوم والأكل.
Can't sleep,
لا أستطيع النوم
for the good of the empress,
من أجل خير الإمبراطورة ،
I'll punish the empress
سأعاقب الإمبراطورة
for five days not to eat meat.
لمدة خمسة أيام عدم أكل اللحوم.
Ah,
آه،
Don't eat meat for five days,
لا تأكل اللحم لمدة خمسة أيام ،
Qin Molin,
تشين مولين ،
You black-bellied devil.
أنت شيطان ذو بطن أسود.